smartcpc.com 2007-10-12

# SmartCPC.com — Intelligent Online Marketing: Privacy

SmartCPC.com Inc. ("SmartCPC.com") respects the privacy of those who use the SmartCPC.com website (the "SmartCPC.com service"). Information that relates to any individual will not be not intentionally disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission, as explained in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy"). 

### What Information Do We Collect?

SmartCPC.com does not collect any unique information about you through the cookie process (such as your name, email address, etc.), except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information; whether you have a query or are registering for the SmartCPC.com service. SmartCPC.com notes and saves information such as time of day, browser type, browser language, and IP address with each query. That information is used to verify our records and to provide more relevant services to users. 

### Links to Other Sites

From time to time, SmartCPC.com may display links to sites that are developed by people over whom SmartCPC.com exercises no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. SmartCPC.com may choose to exhibit these links as an "URL redirecter." When SmartCPC.com uses a URL redirecter, if you click on a URL, information about the click is sent to SmartCPC.com , and SmartCPC.com in turn sends you to the site you clicked on. SmartCPC.com uses this URL information to understand and improve the quality of SmartCPC.com 'S technology and for advertising effectiveness purposes. 

### Do We Share Information?

SmartCPC.com will not share information about you with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. Notwithstanding the aforementioned, please be aware, however, that we will release specific personal information about you if required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order. 

### Consent and changes to the Privacy Policy

By using the SmartCPC.com service, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this policy and to our Terms and Conditions Policy. SmartCPC.com may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. By submitting your application, you are consenting to be contacted by an account representative of Smart Web, Inc. Such contact may be made by email or via phone, even if you have listed yourself on a Do-Not-Call Registry. 

### Additional questions?

Contact us any time and we'll answer any additional questions you may have. Our email address is [support@SmartCPC.com](mailto:support@SmartCPC.com). 

Updated January 26, 2006
